[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以在使用DOM时，性能是一个巨大的问题。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So performance is a huge problem in working with the DOM.
每次你接触一个节点，你付出了巨大的时间惩罚。
Every time you touch a node, you pay a huge time penalty.
重新设计有很大的成本。
Restyling has a big cost.
回流有很大的成本。
Reflowing has a big cost.
重新粉刷有很大的成本。
Repainting has a big cost.
像节点列表这样的随机事物可能会有巨大的成本。
Random things like node lists can have a huge cost.
节点列表看起来像一个数组，只是每次触摸它时都会重复
A node list looks like an array except every time you touch it it can repeat
导致它出现的查询可能非常昂贵。
the query that caused it to come into existence which can be wildly expensive.
事实证明，在大多数应用程序中，JavaScript的成本非常低。
And it turns out in most applications JavaScript has a very small cost.
所以如果你把所有的时间都花在浏览器上，然后说，这就像
So if you took all the time that's being spent in the browser and say, this much as
解析，这个就像编组，这个就像呈现等等。
parsing, this much as marshalling, this much as rendering and so on.
JavaScript将会非常类似，但我看到人们在追求他们的代码，
JavaScript will be like that much but I see people going after their code,
试着把它缩小得更多，而且
trying to shrink it down more, and more, and
更多的时候，所有这些其他的东西都需要时间。
more when it's all this other stuff that's taking the time.
尝试优化它，如果JavaScript引擎的速度是无限快的话
Trying to optimize that, if JavaScript engines were infinitely fast
大多数Web应用程序的运行速度都差不多。
most web applications would run about the same speed.
没人会注意到有什么不同。
No one would notice any difference.
因此，除非有好的工具，否则无法优化性能。
So you can't optimize for performance unless you have good tools.
不幸的是，我们现在有一些好的工具。
Unfortunately, we now have some good tools.
例如，Chrome上有速度跟踪器。
For example, there's speed tracer on Chrome.
当您的应用程序在浏览器中运行时，它会记录Micro Density。
It records micro dense as your application is running in the browser.
完成后，你可以做尸检分析
And when it's done, you can then do a post-mortem analysis and
它将向您显示代码中的所有热点以及消耗时间的内容。
it will show you all the hotspots in the code and what is consuming time.
有了这些信息，他们就有可能优化应用程序。
And with that information it is possible to them optimize the application.
微软有一个类似的东西叫做性能仪表板，我认为
Microsoft has a similar thing called performance dashboard which I think
开始在IE 11上可用。
starts becoming available on IE 11.
没有良好性能数据的优化是浪费时间。
Optimization without good performance data is a waste of time.
事实证明，少量的JavaScript就可以转换DOM
It turns out that a small amount of JavaScript can transform the DOM
只是世界上最糟糕的API之一，变成了令人愉快和富有成效的东西。
just one of the world's awfullest APIs into something pleasant and productive.
所以Ajax库既有趣又容易制作，这就是为什么会有这么多这样的库。
So Ajax libraries are fun and easy to make which is why there are so many of them.
任何应用程序都应该使用一个。
Any apps should be using one.
它们提供了可移植性，因为浏览器是如何实现的，非常不一致。
They provide portability because the browser is how, are hugely inconsistent.
因此您需要一个库来处理这些不一致的问题
And so you need a library that will deal with those inconsistencies for
你这样你就可以和一个更好的模特一起工作了。
you so you can be working with a much better model.
它们提供了对DOM的def规范中的错误的纠正。
They provide correction of errors that are in the def specification of the DOM.
它们提供了更高的编程模型，
They provide a much higher programming model,
一些可以让你更有效率的事情。
something where you can be much more productive.
而且它们还提供了一组小部件，可以简化您的开发工作。
And they also provide sets of widgets, which can simplify your development work.
那你怎么选择？
So how do you choose?
外面有这么多图书馆。
There are so many libraries out there.
对所有现有库进行完整评估需要更长的时间
It would take longer to do a complete evaluation of all the existing libraries
而不是从头开始建立一个新的。
than to build a new one from scratch.
我不建议任何人从头开始构建一个新的。
I don't recommend that anybody build a new one from scratch.
所以几年前，阿贾克斯人建议投掷飞镖
So some years ago the Ajaxians suggested throw a dart
因为随便挑一个，他们都很棒，而且都好得多
cuz just picking one at random they're all pretty good and they're all much better
而不是直接和DOM交谈，这样你就不会输了，随便挑一个就行了。
than talking to the DOM directly so you can't lose, just pick one at random.
问题是每一个都是陷阱
The problem with that is that each one is a trap,
它们都是彼此极不相容的。
that they are all extremely incompatible with each other.
事实上，从一个版本到另一个版本，有些版本与自己不兼容。
In fact some are incompatible with themselves from one version to another.
某物的第一点可能与第二点完全不相容
That point one of something might be completely incompatible with point two of
某件事，一旦你陷入其中一件事，你就被卡住了。
something, and once you get into one of these things you are stuck.
它是由焦油制成的，你写的一切都将依赖于这个东西
It's made of tar and everything you write is gonna be dependent on this thing and
从它中解脱出来，去做其他的事情是极其昂贵和痛苦的。
getting loose from it and onto something else is extremely expensive and painful.
那么你是如何决定做什么的呢？
So how do you decide what to do?
几年前我就预测过，市场不能容忍有这样的人
Some years ago I predicted that the market could not tolerate having so
这周围的许多图书馆都将不得不进行一次洗牌。
many of these libraries around that there is gonna have to be a shakeout.
我预测他们都会消失，也许会有两个赢家。
And I predicted that they'd would all disappear the be maybe two winners.
其中一个可能是微软，
One of them was probably gonna be Microsoft,
因为赢家之一总是微软。
because one of the winners is always Microsoft.
一个是其他东西，PlayWire、Dojo或jQuery或其他东西。
And one would be something else, PlayWire, Dojo or jQuery or something.
结果证明这是完全错误的。
That turned out to be completely wrong.
从那时起，图书馆的数量只增加了。
The number of libraries has only increased since then.
第一个失败的图书馆
And the first library to fail and
完全退出市场的是微软的Atlas
completely leave a market was Microsoft's Atlas which was so
糟糕的是，即使他们不能使用它，他们切换到jQuery。
bad even they couldn't use it and they switched to jQuery.
那你怎么决定？
So how do you decide?
这是一个非常困难的问题，我没有解决方案。
And it's a really hard problem and I do not have a solution.
我们发现越来越多的图书馆一直在线，
And we find more libraries coming online all the time,
更多的平台，更多的做事方式。
more platforms, more ways of doing stuff.
我觉得我跟不上这些东西。
And I thought I can't keep up with the stuff.
那你怎么选择？
So how do you choose?
我没有什么好的建议，除了这个它是值得的。
I have no good advice except this for what it's worth.
询问JSLint，选择您正在考虑通过JSLint运行的任何候选人。
Ask JSLint, take any candidates that you're considering run through JSLint.
这是代码质量的客观度量。
That's an objective measure of code quality.
它会给你同样的指示写的东西有多好。
It will give you same indication how well the things written.
也许这对你有意义。
Maybe that's meaningful to you.